Hello everyone, I am Xueli.
I believe everyone has already known that Marvelous Designer and Lurtis Studios have held a 3D asset competition together.
Next, I will explain in this video how to sign up and what to do after joining the Discord channel.
First, let's take a look at the competition rules and introductions.
After logging into Marvelous Designer's official website, scroll down and find the news interface.
In the news interface, find the news of Lurtis and Marvelous Designer.
After clicking, we can see that this page has been opened.
The window that opens is actually a brief introduction to our competition.
Here it is written in full English, so I will translate it for you.
First of all, our competition is called the monthly 3D asset adjustment.
In this competition, it is a competition that will be held every month.
This competition has been held since May 2022.
The theme of each month's competition is different.
Before we sign up, we will announce the theme of this month's competition.
It is usually announced at the end of the month.
At the end of the month, we will announce the theme of the next month.
After the announcement, you can start to create your own 3D assets based on this theme.
The 3D assets here are not limited to 3D clothing.
You can also use props or some materials.
If you miss the registration time, don't worry.
You can also participate in the registration of the next month.
Our competition will continue until the end of 2022.
You can visit the activity page below.
We will introduce the activity page later.
Next, let's take a look at some of the awards in this competition.
First of all, the awards in this competition are divided into two categories.
One is the basic award, and the other is the special selection award.
The special selection award is named after the exclusive rating of Marvelous Designer.
Therefore, if you want to participate in the selection of the special selection award,
you need to use Marvelous Designer to complete your work.
Of course, you can also combine other 3D software to make it.
As for the Marvelous Designer special selection award, you will receive the following two prizes.
First, you will get one year of the personal version of Marvelous Designer.
Second, you can get a gift card worth 200 US dollars from Steam or Google Play.
These two gift cards are optional.
Next, we can see the 1st, 2nd, and 3rd prize.
Here we can see that the prize is very rich.
I hope everyone can participate in this competition more.
Next, let's take a look at the competition page.
At the top of the competition page, you can see the theme of each game.
Because the theme of each month is different,
so before everyone participates in the competition,
remember to go to the competition page first to see what the theme of this game is.
Next is the name of this game.
Next is the time of registration.
Next is the date of registration.
Therefore, when I recorded the video,
my episode ended on June 5th.
So everyone needs to confirm it.
The next button is to visit the Discord channel of our competition.
This is a real-time chat software.
A lot of news was released on this software this time.
And it is necessary to use this software.
So please remember to register and log in.
Next is the time of each month of this competition.
First, at the end of each month,
we will open the registration of the next month's competition.
After the theme of the new game is announced,
you can register in Discord.
After registration is complete,
at the beginning of next month,
you can submit the competition work.
For example, if you register at the end of May,
you can start submitting the competition work at the beginning of June.
In this video I recorded,
you can start submitting the work on June 5th.
Submitting works also need to be done on Discord.
Then there is our submission deadline.
Let me remind you again.
Remember to participate in the Discord channel of this game.
If you haven't participated in the Discord channel before the deadline,
I'm sorry.
Your participation work will not be submitted.
Also, remember to register for the competition first.
If you don't register for the competition,
you can't submit the competition work directly.
About how to register for the competition
and where to submit the competition work,
we will talk about it later.
At the end of the month,
we will announce the total of the points submitted by the back-end judges.
Then we will select the winning work.
Next, let's take a look at the rules of this competition.
First, you must ensure that the design concept of this competition work
is created by you.
If the concept of art is from someone else,
you must submit the authorization book
that was written by the original owner of the concept of art.
Second, all models must be submitted at the same time.
All model materials must be your own independent design.
If it is a model or material created by someone else,
it must be very, very different from the source.
Then you can continue to use it.
We strongly recommend you to use your own independent design.
Third, all 3D software and material production software can be used.
If Marvelous Designer is used in the process of creating this 3D asset,
then you can participate in the selection of Marvelous Designer.
Fourth, the contestant needs to create based on the theme of this competition.
The 3D asset of creation must be based on the game project.
In other words, please try to ensure that your competition work
is in line with the game production process.
This also means that the work you submit
is best if it has a better core structure.
Fifth, the rendering must be rendered in the 8-hole or other real-time rendering engine.
Here, the real-time rendering engine can be Unreal,
8-hole or Unity, etc.
Sixth, adjust your final rendering product in Photoshop.
Seventh, please be sure to comply with some of the rules and rules
and regulations set by Lurtis Studios in this competition.
These rules include rules that are not limited to the competition page,
as well as some use rules in Discord.
Please note that if you do not comply with these rules,
you may be disqualified from the competition.
Eighth, if the contestant does not sign up in advance
or does not join the Discord channel,
he or she will not be able to get the points.
So once again, please remember to join our Discord channel.
At the bottom is our review introduction.
If you scroll down,
you will see our 1st, 2nd, and 3rd prize presentations.
Next, let's take a look at how to use Discord.
First of all, Discord is a chat software.
In this chat software platform,
you can see some announcements released by the official platform.
In addition, you can communicate and chat with other users
who are concerned about this channel.
In the competition page,
click and enter the official Discord channel of Lurtis Studios.
After entering, click on Rules on the left,
you will see some of the rules used by the official channel.
After clicking, you can see the introductions of different groups.
We can switch these groups
by clicking on the title names near the arrow keys on the far left.
The contents of different groups are different.
For example, you can see some announcements in Announcement.
Technical questions are some technical questions
that can be asked in it.
Or you can share your homepage,
let more artists know and communicate with you,
or you can upload your recruitment information in some channels, etc.
Later, including us submitting our works,
it also needs to be completed in these groups.
The following are the rules about the channel.
The first one is some of the official rules of Discord.
You need to abide by them.
You can refer to them by clicking the link next to it.
The second rule is that
during the whole process of the competition,
please make sure that the names of your Discord
and the nicknames or real names on ArtStation
are written in English.
Because this competition is a global competition,
in order to integrate these information better,
please use English during the whole process of the competition.
The next rule is that
do not add everyone in the group or channel,
and do not share other information
in the official Discord channel of this competition.
Please share other Discord channels
or other external groups.
The fifth rule is that
ban any illegal activities,
including but not limited to
plagiarism, plagiarism,
other people's works, etc.
The sixth rule is that
during the process of communicating with others,
please be respectful and professional.
The seventh rule is that
please do not harass others
or post some insulting information.
The eighth rule is that
please avoid discussing political-related sensitive information.
The ninth rule is that
please post appropriate information
in a suitable group.
For example,
if you want to share your main business,
please share your work and main business
in the channel called Portfolio Share.
The last rule is that
if you want to promote your work
or your product,
please communicate with the management of the channel in advance
and only after you have obtained the permission
can it be released.
Next, let's take a look at
a few more important groups.
First of all, let's come to the challenge,
which is the announcement below the game,
which is our announcement group.
After coming to this group,
you will see that
our official staff
will post some relevant information here.
For example, in my video,
we can see that
in this channel,
we may say that
the date of the last day of submitting works
has been changed.
Now we have changed to the
11.59 p.m. on June 20.
Please note that
the time we mentioned here
is Taiping Yang time.
Of course, in this group,
when we share some important information,
we will add all people,
so you can pay close attention
to the content in this announcement column.
Next, let's take a look at the previous announcement.
At the end of the month,
we will usually publish
the registration link for the next month.
Here we can see the enrollment link,
which is our registration link.
Click on it,
and we can start to register.
Next to it is our competition page.
At the bottom,
you can see
a picture of its main introduction.
Let's go up again
to see what other announcement content there is.
Here we will see
that at the end of the month,
we will announce
some rules that you need to abide by
when you submit your work.
Next, let's take a look at
what are the rules of submission.
Of course, please note that
there may be some changes
to the subsequent submission rules.
Please pay attention to the announcement
in this group.
The first rule of submission is
that each contestant
needs to use a watermark
that we have created.
This watermark can be found
in the appendix,
and the work needs to be uploaded
to ArtStation.
Therefore,
please register an account
on ArtStation
to publish this contest work.
The second rule is
that when you share your work
on ArtStation,
remember to type
Lurtis Marvelous Challenge
in this label.
Of course, if you don't know,
we will have a page
to show you later.
The third rule is that
after uploading the document
to ArtStation,
there will be a description box
to fill in the description of
your work.
In the description box,
you need to write the following information.
This paragraph
needs to be copied and pasted.
We can see it
on the reference page later.
In simple terms,
this paragraph tells us
that other people
who can see this work
are used to participate in the competition.
Of course,
in addition to the necessary description
that needs to be filled in,
you can also fill in
some other details
about this contest work.
The fourth rule is that
when uploading a picture
of your contest work,
you need at least
three renderings
and at least one transparent frame.
We strongly recommend
you to share more renderings
or share a video.
Next,
let's take a look at
the channel of sharing
your contest work.
On the left,
click on Completed Works.
You can share
your finished work.
After clicking on it,
you can see
the works shared
by previous contestants.
We finally submitted
our own contest work
in this channel.
Here you can see
that our cover picture
uses a unified watermark.
Before sharing
your own contest work,
please make sure
you have registered
in advance.
Now let's click on
a contest work
to see the content
that needs to be included
in this contest work.
First of all,
you can see that
this is the prize work
of our first game,
including the MD Special Award.
After opening it,
we can see that
there will be a series of introductions
at the very beginning
of the information bar.
For this introduction,
you can just
copy and paste it directly.
After copying and pasting
the information about
participating in this game,
you can fill in
other details
to enrich
your introduction content.
At the bottom,
you can mark
the 3D software
you are using.
If you use
Marvelous Designer
in your contest work,
please remember
to mark it.
Here we can see
that in his contest work,
there is a rendering
with multiple angles
and a rendering
video
and a frame
image.
After that,
you can see
that this is
the result
of the presentation.
If you want to
show the details
of the presentation,
such as the rendering
and the frame image,
you can add
as much details
as you can.
These are related
to the contest work.
If you want to sign up,
you can go back
to the registration link
you saw
in our previous
video.
Since this game
will be held
every month,
you must remember
that the registration
you submit
is the registration
of this game.
After opening
this page,
if you are
using Google
browser
and Google account,
the progress
you fill in
will be automatically
saved.
If not,
it doesn't matter.
You just need
to fill in
your own information
according to
the options
he wrote.
After filling in
the email,
you need
to select
the rules
and regulations
on all
Lurtis Studios
at the bottom
.
If you want
to check
these rules,
just click
on the top
page
.
The first thing
I want to
tell you
is to remember
to join
our Discord
channel.
Because all
of our sharing
works are
based on
Discord,
you must
remember
to join
our Discord
channel.
Click Yes
and go to
the next page.
In the next page,
you need to
fill in
some of
your
relevant
information.
Discord's
ID usually
consists of
a name
and a
number
string of
numbers.
Please don't
change
this name
at will.
The bottom
page is
your
full name.
Please
type in
English
at the bottom
.
The bottom
page is
the
personal
homepage
in
your
account.
You can
fill in
your
personal
homepage
by
copying
your
own
homepage
.
Note that
it is
your
homepage
link
and not
your
contest
work
link.
Because
usually
when we
sign up,
the
contest
works